Hello friends, my name is Anil Rajpurohit and this time I am presenting to you
a new product of Bajaj Life Insurance launched in July 2023, Bajaj
Allianz ACE
is called this, so it is also
making itself a name in the insurance industry and has launched an excellent product, the main
feature of this product is that you can take a policy for up to 100 years, you can also take it for 85 years,
if you want, you can also select the policy term according to you, but the
best thing is that here the income starts from the first month and if there
is death of the life insured in the policy, the premiums are waived, the income
continues to come to the nominee and maturity has also come, so
they have launched this unique benefit, so let's understand this whole product, if you like my video, then definitely subscribe to the YouTube channel Anil Rajpurohit FFFS and like it,
now let's understand its remaining features, in these four options which are given, there will be an option of premium
payment term 5 years 6 years 7 8 9, 10 and 12 years You can also select payment for free
from five to 12 years. The policy term in this will be hundred
or 85. It will be different in different options. But for example, in the application income,
you will see how much will be the income period equal to the policy term. If the difference
field you have taken is of 5 years, then do it. Otherwise, your income term
will be equal to the policy term. In this, if you select limited term policy term,
you can take a policy term of 10 years to 45 years. Or you can give the option of online
which will be social or you can select only one
100 and from 10 to 45. If you want to select any policy term of 11, 15, 25,
you can select it. You
can keep it for 5 years.
Talking about wealth, in wealth you will get 10 to 45. If you are taking limited term,
the whole life option is 85. This is the option in almost all of them. If we
talk about the entries, then a person from 18 to 55 years can purchase this policy.
If you have taken the policy with goal protection benefit, I
will explain the meaning of goal production later, I have also explained the full details of goal protection. And if it
is without protection, then any person from zero to 60 years
can purchase this policy. The flexibility of the policy is that the customer can decide himself
how much income he needs, whether he needs it early or late, whether he needs to increase or decrease the income, even then the options are visible.
But for example, we are selecting a 35-year-old person and we
are selecting 10 years of premium payment. And here now look at the option, higher income balance benefit and higher maturity,
where you will see that
you are getting both guaranteed income and cash bonus. So in the first option, what did the customer
select in higher income, that he selected 94% of the early income and separated it from the balance 6%, so
he started earning money of Rs. 38,000 in the second balance. In benefit, he selected 20% belt of early income
80%, so now he has started earning ₹32000,
in the third initial income he kept 60% belt and 40%, so he
has started earning 24000 rupees, so on an income of 38000 the maturity is 93 lakhs, on an income of ₹32000
the maturity is 2 crore 8 lakhs and on an annual income of ₹24000 the maturity
is 3 crore 73 lakhs, so customer can decide himself whether he
wants income in the beginning or more,
so now let us understand the illness of this product, a 35 year old person who
purchases this policy, in which he selects premium payment for 10 years and
the policy term is for full 100 years, people are taking this policy up to hundred and suppose
they want to pay lakh rupees as premium annually in this policy
and Here the option that we are selecting, in early income, their investment will go
94%, in fruit creation, their investment is more six percent
and the policy term is 65 years because if a person of 35 years is ahead, then
it will last for 100 years, so for 65 years, the minimum insurance will be 11 times.
Now here, the good thing is that here in the first year you
get a discount of 2%, so the premium will be 98000, next year GST will be applicable, over 98000,
the first GST is 4.5%, then 2.25% will be applicable, so the premium that comes in the next second and after that
will be 11250. Now we understand that here there are two portions, one is
the portion of guaranteed benefit, this is the guaranteed one and one is the 4 percent table
and one is the 8 percent table,
here in number three,
you will see how much is the survival benefit, 15297
in 11, see where you will get the cashback. 22885 will come and we will try adding both
So in column number 17 you will get 38142, this 38142 will come to you for your entire life
and you will get maturity, what will be the maturity amount, 94 lakh
13775, this will be your maturity amount, when will it be when you have selected that
early income is 94% 6% in your belt, now suppose you have decided that early income
is 80% and wealth is 20%, what will you get, instead of 38000, 32460 will start coming and
on maturity, instead of 94 lakhs, what will you get, 2 crore 9 lakh 8185
option, you have increased now what are you doing
and I want to take another
option, 24000 rupees will start coming for lifetime and your maturity which is till 100 years,
which will give you maturity of about ₹ 3 crore and
you can also see the column of debt benefit, which in the table of 8%, you will get crore rupees Till then it keeps on increasing and
the debt benefit also increases with time. So now you
have seen all the three options till here that how do you want more income or you
want more wealth or you can select it. There is another good option in this that
instead of 100 years if you want to select a shorter policy term like here the customer
decided that I want to keep it at least 30 years in advance i.e. this
policy should be completed by the age of 65 and here there is also an option of payment,
the customer said that I do not want the income from the first year, I want it after 5-6 years, so
what benefit does the customer get, you will notice here
that the customer
has started getting 48218 rupees and this next 30
year policy did not get anything in the first 5 years because the difference was given from 70 years
to 30th year he got 48 thousand and in this he will get ₹20 lakh 490000 on maturity,
so if you take a short policy term If you want to take it till 85, then
I want to take it for 100 years, if you want to take more early income or you
want to take more at the time of death, you can select according to your need
[Sangeet]
Now let's understand the best feature of this policy, its name is Goal
Protection Benefit Goal Protection Benefit In other words,
the policy is of continuous benefit, on your death, the customer who has purchased the policy,
even after his death, the policy continues, the benefits continue,
like if you are a 35 year old person and here he is taking the policy
[Sangeet]
and here in the Early Income option his childhood interest is going and
45% is going in the belt and he has said yes on Goal Protection Benefit, that is,
he has selected this option and his insurance cover is 1 lakh 11 times 11
lakh rupees, on the first side he will get 2% discount, so the premium will be 98000. Now
let's understand here exactly how the benefit is relief,
which is 20277 See in column number 17, this income
will start coming to the customer from the very first year, as if he has
completed all the investments of ₹20,000, ₹270, he will start getting income till 85 years.
But the good thing is that if the mother dies at any time, she may die in the first year,
second year, or five years, let us understand by example that she died on 5th,
she had paid 5 lakh rupees, she died, her insurance tax was 11 lakh
rupees, the family will get it immediately, plus if any amount was accumulated, then 5% of that
will be received, otherwise 11 lakh will be received at least and the remaining 5 premiums remain, the
company says that the company will waive off the payment of all five premiums and this
income of ₹70 from 2002 will keep coming to your nominee for the number of years of income for the remaining children,
and the 1 crore 3 lakh on maturity 10248 are going to be given, they will also
come, if there is no death, you will get ₹77 from 20000 and you
will get a Mercedes worth one crore rupees, if there is death, you will get insurance of 11 lakhs immediately and its
premium payment will be waived and income will continue and maturity will also be available, so all these
taxes will be free, so in this way, this is a unique feature, which
is probably in very few policies in the industry, which give income for such a long time and also
waive the premium and keep the benefit continued, so this is a very good and unique feature, if
we talk about the features inside the policy
in traditional policy, then there is Surinder benefit in it, if you
have paid premium for 2 years or more, then Surinder value will be generated in this policy
and if you want to get Surinder, you can do it,
from the point of view of Surinder, never do any traditional policy, if your objective
is to get Surinder early, then do not do it, if you pay premium in the policy till the full amount,
then there is more benefit in it, only then purchase it If you do it, then decide it first
You will be able to pay the entire premium. We should select only that much premium payment. Secondly, if we look at
non-payment of premium support, if you have paid premium for less than 2 years, that is,
if you have paid premium for only one year and have got the policy
cancelled, then you will not get any benefit. If you have paid the premium on time, then Surinder value
is also generated. Policy RP can also get
the revival of the policy done. If you are not able to pay the premium on time due to any reason, then
you have time till 5 years, by paying late fees etc., you
can get the policy revived. If we talk about income tax, then in this policy, you
will get benefit under section 80C of income tax up to Rs. 10 lakh and the money that is coming back on maturity
will be tax free for you. If we talk about loan in this policy,
because it is a traditional possibility, then you will get loan in it. If we talk about grace period,
then if your policy
is new, then you will get grace period of 30 days. If you purchase it on monthly basis,
then you will get 15 days of free loan period. 15 days are free
after taking the policy. From the time the policy is delivered to your home till 15 days, if you feel
that the features mentioned to you or what you thought were in the policy are not there or for some
other reason, you wanted to cancel the policy so that you can get the entire money back by cancelling
it, there is a rider for virus, there is a rider for accidental death,
there is a rider for disabilities, there is also a rider for family benefit,
there is a rider for family income benefit and critical premium. But for example, a 35-year-old person is
taking a policy term of 30 years, the premium payment term is late for 10 years, the
benefit will last for 10 lakhs, then his premium for 10 years will be only ₹1000,
the benefit will last for 30 years. This rider is maximum 65 years, it lasts only till that. If
we talk about disability rider, then you will get it for just ₹640, you are taking a family income
of 10 lakhs. As for the benefits, here the relief is that whatever
insurance you take here, 1% of this rider
is given to your family as income, that is, what is 1% of 10 lakhs,
10000 rupees will be given every month, if it is 10 years or the policy term,
then you will get that, if suppose this disability
occurs 5 years before it ends, then you will still get income for 10 years, 10000
comes from 420, so purchase according to your need,
now talking about critical illness, here you
get benefit of 11 critical illnesses, but the premium is ₹22000 ₹30, so whether you have to add the rider or not, this addition
depends on the additional premium, you
can add accidental death and disability rider, it is quite cheap, you can add the other two riders according to your need,
so finally if I summarize it, then this is an excellent plane, it
is a unique plane in the industry which We are giving you such an option till the age of 85
that if there is death of your earning member in the family in whose name
the insurance policy is, then you get the insurance tax immediately, the premium payment
is waived, the policy continues, their monthly income continues, if there is monthly income, then
the monthly income continues, maturity is also available, there
is income tax benefit as well, you can design your policy according to your requirement, you
can decide the income according to your requirement, so there are a lot of good features, if you
want to purchase this policy then you can contact me, if you want to know more about this policy
then you can contact me on my mobile number, cancel
with the cancel fee, thank you, so before going to the match,
please do something on my YouTube channel